Margaret Bourke-White Papers
Margaret Bourke-White Papers
- Correspondence-subject files
  - Public Utilities Fortnightly, 1933-1935 (Box 40)
  - Pudovkin, Vsevolod Illarionovich, 1931-1933 (Box 40)
  - Purdue University, 1930-1938 (Box 40)
  - Putnam, George Palmer, 1933-1935 (Box 40)
    See also Earhart, Amelia.
  - Q, 1 folder (Box 40)
  - Quick, Wallace J., 1954-1966; undated (Box 40)
  - Quill and Scroll, 1960 (Box 41)
  - Quinby, E. Jay, 1934-1935 (Box 41)
  - R, 4 folders (Box 41)
  - Rabinovitch, 1935 (Box 41)
  - Random House, 1937-1939; 1967 (Box 41)
  - Ratoff, Gregory, 1944 (Box 41)
  - RCA Victor Company, Inc., 1931-1935; undated (Box 41)
  - Reader's Digest, 1956-1962 (Box 41)
  - Realites, 1961-1966 (Box 41)
  - Red Book Magazine, 1932-1935; undated (Box 41)
  - "Red Republic", See "Eyes on Russia" and "Red Republic" (motion pictures).
  - Redmond, William F., 1932 (Box 42)
  - Reilly, Frank C., 1929-1939; undated (Box 42)
  - [Wm. B.] Remington, Inc., 1931-1937; undated (Box 42)
    See also Ludlum Steel Company.
  - Remington Rand, Inc., 1931-1936 (Box 42)
  - Republic Steel Corporation, 1931-1936; undated (Box 42)
    See also Meldrum and Fewsmith, Inc.
  - Reswick, William, 1930-1940; undated (Box 42)
  - Retzer, Florence Horn, 1955 (Box 42)
  - Rice, Alan, 1935-1936 (Box 42)
  - Rice, Elmer C., 1933-1935 (Box 42)
  - Richardson, Alley & Richards, 1932-1936 (Box 42)
  - Richie, Robert Yarnall, 1934-1938; undated (Box 42)
  - Rickard and Company, 1933-1941; undated (Box 42)
  - Rickenbacker, Eddie (Edward Vernon), 1935-1936 (Box 42)
  - Riegel, Emil Raymond, 1933 (Box 42)
  - Rieker, Jane, 1959-1962; undated (Box 42)
  - Riguin, A. A. and family, 1932-1933 (Box 42)
  - Rindl, Johan, See Gumpertz, Julian.
  - Ringel, Fred James, 1933-1935 (Box 42)
  - Roche, Bettie (employee), 1957-1960 (Box 42)
  - Rochester Chamber of Commerce, 1932 (Box 42)
  - Rockefeller Center, 1935-1941; undated (Box 42)
  - Rogers-Kellogg-Stillson, 1932-1935; undated (Box 42)
  - Rogovin, Milton, 1962 (Box 42)
  - Rohrbach Metall-Flugzeugbau, 1930-1932 (Box 42)
  - [Albert] Romeike & Company, Inc., 1931-1938; undated (Box 42)
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D. and Eleanor B., 1929-1944; also includes correspondence of Mrs. Theodore Roosevelt Jr. (Eleanor B. Alexander-Roosevelt), wife of Franklin's cousin (Box 42)
  - Roper, Elmo, 1943-1971 (Box 42)
  - Rosenbaum Grain Corporation, 1932-1935; undated (Box 42)
  - Rosenberg, James N., 1934-1939 (Box 42)
  - Rosenfeld, Beth and Jay, 1955-1965 (Box 42)
  - Rosenfeld, Irene, 1965 (Box 42)
  - The Rotarian, 1932-1935 (Box 42)
  - Rowe, Edna, undated (Box 43)
  - Royal Typewriter Company, Inc., 1934 (Box 43)
  - Rubenstein, Rafael, 1931-1936; undated (Box 43)
  - Rudge, William Edwin, 1931-1938 (Box 43)
  - Rudie, Robert, 1952-1961; undated (Box 43)
  - Rukeyser, Muriel, 1939 (Box 43)
  - Rumford Press, 1933-1934 (Box 43)
  - Ruthven, Alexander, 1951-1963 (Box 43)
    See also University of Michigan.
  - S-Std, 5 folders (Box 43)
  - Ste-Sz, 2 folders (Box 44)
  - Sadjaia, Kalet, 1933-1937; undated (Box 44)
  - Safranek, Milos, See Leroux, Germaine/Safranek, Miles.
  - Sagendorph, Robb, 1943-1966; undated (Box 44)
  - St. John, Robert, undated (Box 44)
  - St. Peter State Hospital, 1934-1935 (Box 44)
  - Saks-Fifth Avenue, 1931-1940 (Box 44)
  - Salten, Felix, 1931 (Box 44)
  - Samaroff Stokowski, Olga, 1929-1931 (Box 44)
  - Sanger, Margaret, 1923 (Box 44)
  - The Saturday Evening Post, 1931-1959 (Box 44)
  - Sauder, Rae Norden, 1934 (Box 44)
  - Schiller, Gunther, 1932-1964 (Box 44)
  - Schillinger, Joseph, 1933; undated (Box 44)
  - Max Schling, Inc., 1933-1934 (Box 44)
  - Schneider, Alexander "Sasha", 1949-1962; undated; 2 folders (Box 44)
  - Schulke, Flip, 1959 (Box 44)
  - Schwartz, A., 1932-1934 (Box 44)
  - Scripps-Howard Newspapers, 1930-1936 (Box 44)
  - Seid, Herman, 1931-1941; undated (Box 44)
  - Selby Shoe Company, 1934-1937; undated (Box 45)
  - Serlin, Oscar, 1933; undated (Box 45)
  - Shahini, Ranjee, 1961 (Box 45)
  - Sherrod, Robert Lee, 1968 (Box 45)
  - Shouse, Catherine Filene, 1933-1960; undated (Box 45)
  - Simon and Schuster, Inc., 1931-1971; undated; 9 folders (Box 45)
  - Simonson, Lee, 1931-1937; undated (Box 45)
  - Sinclair, Upton, 1933 (Box 45)
  - Skvirsky, Boris, 1932-1933 (Box 45)
  - Smith, Alfred E., 1931 (Box 45)
  - Smith, Bradley, 1965-1969; undated (Box 45)
  - Smith, Dorothy, See Time, Inc.
  - Smith, Margaret (employee), 1936-1961; undated; 6 folders (Box 46)
  - Smithsonian Institute, 1965; undated (Box 46)
  - Snow, Edgar, 1948-1963 (Box 46)
  - Sochurek, Howard, 1960 (Box 46)
  - Society of Woman Geographers, 1938-1969 (Box 46)
  - Soho, Limited, 1936-1939 (Box 46)
  - Sokoloff, Nikolai, 1929-1934; undated (Box 47)
  - Sokolsky, George E., 1934 (Box 47)
  - Sonnenberg, Benjamin, 1933-1939 (Box 47)
    See also Selby Shoe Company.
  - South Africa assignment, 1950 (Box 47)
  - South America assignment, 1936 (Box 47)
  - Southern Summer School for Women Workers in Industry, 1937-1938 (Box 47)
  - Soviet Russia Today, 1932-1939; undated (Box 47)
  - Soviet Union, 1931-1938; 2 folders (Box 47)
  - Spencer, Terry and Leslie, See Time, Inc.
  - Sprackling, Helen, 1931-1939; undated (Box 47)
  - Stanley, Edward "Tuck" and Paulie, 1933-1971; undated (Box 47)
  - State Journal Company, 1932-1933 (Box 47)
  - Statue of Liberty assignment, 1936 (Box 47)
  - Stefansson, Evelyn, 1956 (Box 47)
  - Stefansson, Vilhjalmur, 1933-1939 (Box 47)
  - Steichen, Edward, 1931-1954 (Box 47)
  - Steiner, Ralph, 1929-1940; undated (Box 47)
  - Steinhardt, Laurence, 1941 (Box 47)
  - Stern, Alfred, See Dodd, Martha.
  - Stern, Seymour, 1933-1934 (Box 47)
  - Sternau, Herbert and Polly, 1939-1971; undated (Box 48)
  - Stieglitz, Alfred, See O'Keeffe, Georgia.
  - Stiles, Vivien, See Time, Inc.
  - Stone, Hannah M., 1937 (Box 48)
  - Stowe, Leland, 1969 (Box 48)
  - Streit, Clarence K., 1958-1963 (Box 48)
  - Strode, Hudson, 1938 (Box 48)
  - Strong, Anna Louise, 1933 (Box 48)
  - Stryker, Roy E., 1928-1939 (Box 48)
  - Stuart, Charles E., 1933 (Box 48)
  - Studebaker Corporation, 1931 (Box 48)
  - Studin, Charles, 1932-1939 (Box 48)
  - Studio Publications, Inc., 1932-1938 (Box 48)
  - Sudeten German Party, 1938 (Box 48)
  - Sullivan, Harry Stack, 1931-1939 (Box 48)
  - Sullivan, Thelma D., 1966 (Box 48)
  - Swank, Luke, undated (Box 48)
  - Swayze, John Cameron, 1953 (Box 48)
  - Swift and Company, 1929-1934; undated (Box 48)
  - Swing, Raymond, 1937-1939; undated (Box 48)
  - Syracuse University, 1964-1976 (Box 48)
  - Szilasi, Bela and Alix, 1931-1941; undated (Box 48)
  - T, 3 folders (Box 48)
  - Taggard, Genevieve, 1934-1937; undated (Box 49)
  - Taliesin, 1931-1933 (Box 49)
  - Tauber, Edward, 1964 (Box 49)
  - Tausig, Lilian B., See New Masses. (Box 49)
  - Taylor, Clarence R."Tony", 1931-1959; undated (Box 49)
  - The Technological Review, 1931-1936 (Box 49)
  - Teleki, Paul, 1939 (Box 49)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1934-1941 (Box 49)
  - Terminal Tower Company, 1962-1963 (Box 49)
  - Thacker, Earl M., 1939 (Box 49)
  - Theatre Arts Committee, 1932-1939; undated (Box 49)
  - Theatre Guild, Inc., 1931-1941 (Box 49)
  - Theatre Guild Magazine, 1929-1932 (Box 49)
  - Theatre Union, 1932-1934 (Box 49)
  - Thomas, Jean, 1960-1964 (Box 49)
  - Thomas, Lowell, 1938-1944 (Box 49)
  - Thompson, Clara, 1934-1956; undated (Box 49)
  - Thompson, Dorothy, 1945 (Box 49)
  - Thompson, Edward K., See Time, Inc.
  - [J. Walter] Thompson Company, 1932-1957 (Box 49)
  - Throckmorton, Cleon and Juliet, 1931-1967 (Box 49)
  - Time, Inc., 1929-1937; 2 folders (Box 49)
  - Time, Inc., 1938-1955; 7 folders (Box 50)
    See also Smith, Margaret.
  - Time, Inc., 1956-1971; undated; 8 folders (Box 51)
  - Tisse, Edouard, 1933-1934; undated (Box 52)
  - Train, Arthur, 1932; 1942 (Box 52)
  - Transcontinental & Western Air, Inc. (TWA), 1935-1941; undated (Box 52)
  - Treacy, Eleanor, See Time, Inc.
  - Tretiakov, Sergei Mikhailovich and Olga, 1931 (Box 52)
  - Tudor City, 1932-1937; undated (Box 52)
  - Tyrwhitt, Jaqueline, 1957 (Box 52)
  - U, 2 folders (Box 52)
  - Ulmer, Ernest, 1962 (Box 52)
  - Union Trust Company, 1928-1932; undated (Box 52)
    See also Stryker, Roy.
  - Unionbild GMBH, 1932-1933 (Box 52)
  - United Foundation, 1950-1951 (Box 52)
  - United Nations, 1962-1963 (Box 52)
  - United Press, 1931-1939; undated (Box 52)
    See also Kuh, Frederick.
  - United States. Department of Labor, 1933-1970 (Box 52)
  - United States. National Recovery Administration (NRA), 1933-1935 (Box 52)
  - United States. Works Progress Administration, 1936-1938 (Box 52)
  - United States Information Agency, 1944-1966 (Box 52)
  - United States Information Service, 1964-1966; undated (Box 52)
    See also Knittel, Robert/Rainer, Luise.
  - University of Miami Photojournalism Conference, 1958-1959; undated (Box 52)
    See also American Society of Magazine Photographers.
  - University of Michigan, 1928-1971; undated (Box 52)
  - Urey, Harold Clayton, 1939 (Box 52)
  - V, 1 folder (Box 53)
  - Vacuum Oil Company, 1931 (Box 53)
  - Valenti, Fernando, 1959 (Box 53)
  - Van Beuren Corporation, 1934-1936 (Box 53)
  - Van Dusen, William D. and Hazel, 1934-1937; undated (Box 53)
    See also Pan American Airways.
  - Van Dyke, Willard, 1938 (Box 53)
  - Van Fleet, James A., 1953 (Box 53)
  - Vanity Fair, 1931-1935 (Box 53)
  - Van Kleeck, Mary, 1934-1938 (Box 53)
  - Van Sweringen (Union Terminal), 1931-1939 (Box 53)
  - Vassos, John and Ruth, 1931-1963; undated (Box 53)
  - Vestal, David, 1965 (Box 53)
  - Viking Press, 1930-1939 (Box 53)
  - Villard, Oswald Garrison, 1932 (Box 53)
  - Volunteer Service Photographers, Inc., 1954-1964 (Box 53)
  - Vondermuhll, Valerie, See Time, Inc.
  - Von Seeckt, Hans, 1933 (Box 53)
  - Vu, 1931-1934 (Box 53)
  - W-Wh, 3 folders (Box 53)
  - Wi-Wz, 3 folders (Box 54)
  - WOR, 1931-1957; undated (Box 54)
  - Walden Book Shop, 1931-1932 (Box 54)
  - [Hiram] Walker & Sons, Inc., 1934-1935 (Box 54)
  - Waller, Helen Hiett, See Hiett, Helen.
  - Walters, Emile, 1935 (Box 54)
  - Ward, Henry Baldwin, 1937 (Box 54)
  - Washington and Lee University, 1938-1939 (Box 54)
  - Washington assignment, 1934-1935 (Box 54)
  - Weinberg, Robert Charles, 1932 (Box 54)
  - Weiss, Julius, 1932-1968; undated (Box 54)
  - Wershba, Joe, 1963-1969; undated (Box 54)
  - Wertenbaker, Lael Tucker, 1963 (Box 54)
  - Wertheim, Maurice, 1935-1938; undated (Box 55)
  - West Point Manufacturing Co., 1936-1937 (Box 55)
  - Western Electric Company, 1935-1939; undated (Box 55)
  - Western Union Telegraph Company, 1932-1935; undated (Box 55)
  - Weston, Edward, 1936; 1960 (Box 55)
  - Weston, Harold and Faith, 1933-1935; undated (Box 55)
  - Westover, Wendall, 1931-1937 (Box 55)
  - Weygant, (Sister) M. Noemi, 1963-1965 (Box 55)
  - White, Cynthia, 1935-1944 (Box 55)
  - White, Minnie and Joseph (parents), See Correspondence-subject files: Family.
  - White, Roger (brother), See Correspondence-subject files: Family.
  - White, Ruth (sister), See Correspondence-subject files: Family.
  - [Clarence H.] White School of Photography, undated (Box 55)
  - [Wm. A.] White & Sons, 1934-1936 (Box 55)
    See also Grimm, Peter.
  - White Company Ltd., 1931 (Box 55)
  - White House Festival of the Arts, 1965 (Box 55)
  - Wieman, Regina Westcott, 1938-1939 (Box 55)
  - Wiley, Louis, 1932-1935; undated (Box 55)
  - Wilhelm, Donald, 1932-1937; undated (Box 55)
  - Wilkinson, Richard G., 1964; undated (Box 55)
  - Williams, Alford, 1936; undated (Box 55)
  - Williams, Gluyas, 1937-1939; undated (Box 55)
  - [Alfred N.] Williams Co., 1934 (Box 55)
  - Willoughby's, 1932-1936 (Box 55)
  - Witkin, Lee D., 1970 (Box 55)
  - Wolf, Friedrich, 1935 (Box 55)
  - Woman's Home Companion, 1931; 1955 (Box 55)
  - Wood, Thomas, 1937-1941 (Box 55)
  - Wood and Wood, 1930-1936; undated (Box 55)
  - Workers Film and Photo League, 1933-1934 (Box 55)
  - World's Work, 1930-1931 (Box 55)
  - Wright, Frank Lloyd, See Taliesin.
  - Wright, Russel, 1932-1934 (Box 55)
  - Wright, Teresa, undated (Box 55)
  - Wurlitzer, Rudolph, 1929-1938 (Box 55)
  - Wurm, Werner, 1964 (Box 55)
  - Y, 1 folder (Box 56)
  - Yakhontoff, Victor A., 1934-1937 (Box 56)
  - Yeomans, Edward, 1935; undated (Box 56)
  - Yim, Louise, 1963 (Box 56)
  - Yolen, Will H., 1953-1963 (Box 56)
  - Young and Rubicam, 1932-1938 (Box 56)
  - Young Women's Christian Association, 1931-1964 (Box 56)
  - Yudewitz, Hyman, 1930-1936; undated (Box 56)
  - Z, 1 folder (Box 56)
  - [Carl] Zeiss, Inc., 1937-1958 (Box 56)
  - Zonta International, 1937; undated (Box 56)
  - Unidentified, incoming (by date) (Box 56)
  - Unidentified, outgoing (by date) (Box 56)
- Glass plates
  Glass plate negatives are currently out for digitization and not accessible to staff or researchers.
  Most of these are undated and appear to be early personal photographs. Most are of the University of Michigan and surrounding areas, or of Russian factories, towns, and people. There are also unidentified landscapes, bridges, people, and several of ferns. Mixed in with the glass plates are a few copy negatives, color separation plates, color positives, and at least one print.
  - Miscellaneous, scenes from University of Michigan (Alumni Memorial, Clements Library, Commencement); "Baby Jack"; Chubb's Orchestra; bridges; 20 items (Oversize 144 / 1)
  - Miscellaneous, scenes from University of Michigan (Commencement, Hill Auditorium, Law building, Martha Cook, Zeta Psi); fountain; gargoyles; girls in "tap room"; galoshes; invitations to Helen Newberry event; L. Kessinger; 20 items (Oversize 144 / 2)
  - Miscellaneous, scenes from University of Michigan (museum, Alumni Memorial Hall, Natural Science building, Newberry Hall, Physics Building); Purdue Union; Detroit railway station; river from Whitmore Lake Bridge; quarry near Ypsilanti; kilts; short wave oscillator; snow on campus/Japanese berries; spring games, freshmen and sophomores; 19 items (Oversize 144 / 3)
  - Miscellaneous, spring games, sophomores; square waterfall on Huron; summar school campus views; unidentified buildings and landscapes; unidentified people; Michigan Union; walk to museum; 20 items (Oversize 144 / 4)
  - Miscellaneous, Yost field house [University of Michigan] from press stand; ferns; original envelopes; Russian Iron Puddler" from Red October Rolling Mills; 10 items (Oversize 144 / 5)
  - Miscellaneous, probably Russia, accordion player, young woman in profile, young girl with purse, women gathered by statue, children in classroom, portrait of mustachioed worker; workers with machinery; woman holding child; structure over water; bridge; dancing children; farm equipment; unidentified landscapes; babies; workers at loom; 25 items (Oversize 144 / 6)
  - Miscellaneous Russia (Stalingrad, Magnetogorsk, etc.), workers at loom; Russian Orthodox church; workers at machines, assembly line, on the street, in workers' club; foreman at drill; children; iron puddlers from Red October Rolling Mills; man on turbine shell; miner pushing cart; camel caravan; etc; 25 items (Oversize 144 / 7)
  - Miscellaneous industry-related, probably Russia, miners with cart, girl conductor, industrial landscapes, men on turbine, etc.; 5 items (Oversize 144 / 8)
  - "Bound Brook House", 8x10 glass plate negatives with contact prints; 3 items (Oversize 144 / 9)
  - MBW in red hat, full color (color positive); Grapes "Red 71" (color separation plate); shoe sets for Vanity Fair "1447", "1448", and "1449" (color separation plates); Eastern Airline [EAL] aerial image, 6 items (Oversize 144 / 10)
- Memorabilia
  - Financial
    - Banking records, 1933-1957; 6 folders (Box 73)
    - Banking records, 1957-1958; 5 folders (Box 74)
    - Banking records, 1962-1971; 2 folders (Box 75)
    - Bills and receipts, 1931-1941; 3 folders (Box 75)
    - Bills and receipts, 1951-1971; undated; 3 folders (Box 76)
    - Employee salaries, 1940-1966 (Box 76)
    - Expense accounts with Time, Inc., 1936-1956 (Box 76)
    - Profit-sharing plan with Time, Inc., 1954-1971 (Box 76)
    - Royalty statements, 1931-1971 (Box 77)
    - Social Security, 1966-1969 (Box 77)
    - Stocks, 1932-1971 (Box 77)
    - Studio records
      - Bills and receipts, 1928-1941; undated (Box 77)
      - Bills and receipts (bound), 1931-1933 (Box 77)
      - Office financial records, 1934-1937 (Box 77)
      - Petty cash receipts, 1933-1934 (Box 77)
      - Petty cash receipts (cont.), 1933-1934 (Box 78)
      - Production and delivery orders, 1932-Nov. 1934; 7 folders (Box 78)
      - Production and delivery orders, Nov. 1934-Feb. 1935; 6 folders (Box 79)
      - Production and delivery orders, Feb. 1935-May 1935; 6 folders (Box 80)
      - Production and delivery orders, May. 1935-Aug. 1935; 7 folders (Box 81)
      - Production and delivery orders, Sept. 1935-Apr. 1936; 8 folders (Box 82)
      - Production and delivery orders, May 1936-Oct. 1936; undated; 5 folders (Box 83)
      - Shipping orders and packing slips, 1933-1937 (Box 83)
      - Statements, 1931-1935 (Box 83)
    - Taxes, Cleveland, 1931-1932 (Box 83)
    - Taxes, New York State sales, 1933-1938 (Box 83)
    - Taxes, income, 1931-1956; 3 folders (Box 83)
    - Taxes, income, 1957-1971; 3 folders (Box 84)
    - Miscellaneous, 1930-1958; 1969 (Box 84)
  - Legal
    - Contracts and agreements - trust with power of attorney, 1967-1969 (Box 84)
    - Contracts and agreements, misc., 1931-1971 (Box 84)
    - Insurance, accident and liability, 1930-1971 (Box 84)
    - Insurance, auto, 1957-1967 (Box 84)
    - Insurance, home and property, 1932-1971 (Box 84)
    - Insurance, life
      - New York Life Insurance Company, 1924-1965 (Box 84)
      - Provident Mutual Life Insurance Company of Philadelphia, 1937-1957 (Box 85)
      - Prudential Insurance Company, 1936-1968 (Box 85)
      - Ruth White's life insurance, 1961 (Box 85)
    - Insurance, medical, 1952-1966 (Box 85)
    - Insurance, miscellaneous, 1934-1966; 2 folders (Box 85)
    - Leases, 1932-1959 (Box 85)
    - Studio releases, 1931-June 1934 (Box 85)
    - Studio releases, July 1934-1936; undated; 3 folders (Box 86)
    - Wills, 1964-1968 (Box 86)
    - Miscellany, 1930-1965 (Box 86)
  - Printed material
    - Books
      - The American Annual of Photography 1930, Transferred to Rare Books for cataloging.
      - Martha's Vineyard, 1970; photographs / Alfred Eisenstaedt; text / Henry Beetle Hough (Box 87)
      - Pictorial Hyderabad Vol. I / K. Krishnaswamy Mudiraj, 1929 (Box 87)
      - Pictorial Hyderabad Vol. II / K. Krishnaswamy Mudiraj, 1934 (Box 87)
      - "Progress" in the Graphic Arts / T. M. Cleland, 1950 (Box 87)
      - Sechzig Choralgesange von Johann Sebastian Bach, 1920 (Box 87)
      - Something Is Missing... / Arthur Goodfriend, 1955 (Box 87)
    - Clippings
      - MBW General, 1927-1937; 9 folders (Box 88)
      - MBW General, 1938-1943; 6 folders (Box 89)
      - MBW General, 1943-1947; 5 folders (Box 90)
      - MBW General, 1948-1953; 7 folders (Box 91)
      - MBW General, 1954-1959; 6 folders (Box 92)
      - MBW General, 1960-1963; 6 folders (Box 93)
      - MBW General, 1963-1971; undated; 9 folders (Box 94)
      - India (Box 95)
      - Life, 4 folders (Box 95)
      - PM, 2 folders (Box 96)
      - Soviet Union (Box 96)
      - Miscellaneous, 1 folder (Box 96)
      - Miscellaneous, 4 folders (Box 97)
    - Exhibition catalogs (miscellaneous), See Correspondence-Subject Files: Exhibition catalogs (miscellaneous).
    - Periodicals (by title)
      - A-F (except The Central European Observer), 4 folders (Box 98)
      - The Central European Observer, vol. XVI nos. 25-26, Dec. 16, 1938 (Oversize 25)
      - G-P, 5 folders (Box 99)
      - Q-T, 4 folders (Box 100)
      - U-Z, 2 folders (Box 101)
    - Miscellany
      - Educational materials (Box 101)
      - Pamphlets on photography (Box 101)
      - Pamphlets, miscellaneous (Box 102)
      - A-Z (except Memories of Bapu) (Box 102)
      - Memories of Bapu (Oversize 25)
  - Scrapbooks
    - "Album 3 - 'Say' 'Russia' ", 1938; Jan. 1941-Sept. 1941; 2 volumes (Oversize 26)
    - American Federationist, 1930-1934; 1942-1945,; 1948-1949; 3 volumes (Oversize 27)
    - Scrapbook [1], contents, 1933-1934 (Oversize 28)
    - Scrapbook [1], covers, 1933-1934 (Oversize 29)
    - "Album 1" contents, 1936 (Oversize 30)
    - "Album 1" covers, 1936 (Oversize 31)
    - Scrapbooks [2] contents, 1936-1938 (Oversize 32)
    - Scrapbooks [2] covers, 1936-1938 (Oversize 33)
    - "ReBk - Album 2" contents, 1937-1938 (Oversize 34)
    - "ReBk - Album 2" covers, 1937-1938 (Oversize 35)
  - Miscellany
    - Business cards and letterhead, undated (Box 103)
    - Cards by MBW, undated (Box 103)
    - Cartoon flats (Oversize 25)
    - Diary of Victoria Cabrera, MBW's live-in physical therapist, 1954 (Box 103)
    - Filmstrips, Life magazine, "The Connecticut River" and "South Africa and Its Problems"; 2 items (Box 103)
    - "For the World to See: The Life of Margaret Bourke-White" by Jonathan Silverman, book jacket only (Oversize 25)
      A copy of this book has been cataloged in Rare Books.
    - Hats, 2 items (Oversize 24)
    - Identifications and memberships (Box 103)
    - Life exhibition proofs (Oversize 25)
    - Life mounted clipping, June 28, 1963 (Oversize 25)
    - Life proof pages (color and black & white) (Oversize 25)
    - Maps, small, includes some informational travel brochures (Box 103)
    - Maps, large
    - "Margaret Bourke-White: The Humanitarian Vision", booklet about documentary (Box 104)
      See Recordings: Moving image recordings: Margaret Bourke-White: The Humanitarian Vision for VHS and U-Matic tapes of this documentary.
    - Medallion of Pablo Casals/Bach from Prades Bach festival (Box 104)
    - Music / John La Montaine (Oversize 25)
    - Music / "Triolet to a Student of French", words / MBW, music / Robert E. Sherwood (Oversize 25)
    - Name plate (brass) for MBW's camera, in cloth bag (Box 104)
    - Pencil portrait of MBW / Karl E. Johnson (Oversize 25)
    - Photograph-related miscellany, empty envelopes, envelopes with annotations, sheets of unidentified notes, etc. (Box 104)
    - Photography brochures and miscellany (Box 104)
    - Photos / Stuart G. Abbey (Oversize 25)
    - Publicity (Box 104)
    - Publicity, oversize (Oversize 25)
    - Stenographers' notebooks, 1956-1957; 1968; 3 volumes (Box 104)
    - Studio interior design and furnishings (Box 104)
    - Studio plans (Box 104)
    - Theatre (plays and movies) (Box 105)
    - Vacation places (Box 105)
    - War Bonds posters, 2 items (Oversize 25)
    - World War II war record (Box 105)
    - Writings by others
      - Apocalypse / Gordden Link (Box 105)
      - Cameras and Courage - Margaret Bourke-White / Iris Noble, 1973 (Box 105)
      - MBW Goes to a Party / Franklin E. Brill (Box 105)
      - "We Were There" / Sgt. Jack Delaney (Box 105)
      - Sunday Showcase, "Margaret Bourke-White Story" / Joseph Liss, 1959 (Box 105)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 105)
- Photographic equipment
  - Small leather shoulder carrying case (Oversize 36)
  - Contents of small leather shoulder carrying case (Oversize 37)
    1 C.P. Goerz, Berlin Dopp-Anastigmat Series 1B Celor f=420mm lens No. 211510 with engraved words "Fried Krupp A.G., Essen" on the mount
    1 small leather lens case containing 1 Linhof Schneider Kreuznach Tele-xenar lens 1:5, 5/180 No. 2296691
    1 soft leather pouch containing a Carl Zeiss Jena lens No. 2561101 Goerz-Dagor 1:9 f=7.5 cm.
    1 small round metal Harrison Duraline case containing 1 series VIII Wratten orange filter no. 22.
    2 Graphic Model 2 film pack adapters
    5 dark slides
    1 wooden viewer 5U
    1 Schneider-Kreuznach Retina-Longar-Xenon f=4/80 mm lens No. 4309698 in a plastic case
    1 small leather filter case containing 1 Franke & Heidecke, Rollei yellow filter
  - Small zippered leather carpet bag (Oversize 38)